

Zeeshan Nazir

Address:

Street # 01 Mohalla Mughalpura, Samijhabad # 02, Babu atta chaki stop, Piran Gaib road, Multan

Email:

zeshan.mughal93.zn@gmail.com

Phone:

+923003653849 +923157915249

DOB:

May 03, 1993

PROFILE

Human resources representative with experience managing employee benefits, employee hiring and onboarding, performance management and HR records. Reliable and organized team member with the ability to communicate effectively and handle office changes. Skilled at building and maintaining relationships, representing shared company values and managing employees across all levels of an organization. Proficient with HRIS and benefits management.

EDUCATION

Masters: -

MBA (HRM) | Bahauddin Zakariya University, Multan

(2022 - 2024) | CGPA 3.22 / 4

Bachelors: -

BS(Hons) Telecommunication Systems | Bahauddin Zakariya University, Multan

(2012 - 2016) | CGPA 3.32 / 4

HSSC: -

F.S.c (Pre Engineering) | Punjab Group of Colleges, Multan

(2009 – 2011) | Marks 831 / 1100

SSC: -

Matric (Science) | Board of Intermediate & Secondary Education, Multan

(2007 – 2009) | Marks 850 / 1050

Hafiz e Quran | Wafaq-ul-Madaris, Multan

(September 2006) | Marks 87 / 100

WORK HISTORY

IT Support Officer | Pakistan Revenue Automation (Pvt) Limited

August 2022 to Present

Job Responsibilities

- Configuration and Troubleshooting of Router for the Network Connectivity.
- Basic Configuration of Huawei USG6525E Firewall.
- Installation & Configuration of IP Phone and UCM Server (SIP Server).
- Prevention, detection and solution of network problems.
- Installing and Configuration of Domain Controller server.
- Connectivity to the server at branch offices through VPN Software.
- Creating and maintaining user accounts and appropriate access to resources.
- Troubleshoot and resolve different issues relating to Application/Hardware/Network.



- Controlling the Video Conference System
- Solve Internet Connectivity related Issues.
- Providing technical support regarding routing issues.
- Manage and troubleshoot Cisco Routers and Switches.
- Keeping Records in Computer and in File.
- Training to Staff of Using Software.
- Printer Troubleshooting.
- Antivirus Installation and Updating.

Police Communication officer | Punjab Safe Cities Authority, Lahore April 2018 to August 2022

Network Internee | DWP Technologies, Pakistan

January 2015 to July 2015

Internee | National Telecommunication Corporation (NTC), Multan

June 2013 to August 2013



Human Capital Management | Great Learning Academy

August 29, 2023

Introduction to Modern Human Resource Management | Alison Academy

July 04, 2023

Human Resource Management | Great Learning Academy

December 22, 2022

Google Technical Support Fundamentals | Coursera Certificates

December 28, 2022

ACHIEVEMENT

- Commendation Certificate Class-II | Punjab Police
- Certificate of Appreciation | Punjab Safe Cities Authority

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Knowledge of HRMS
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- MS Office

- Strong Computer Skills
- Ability to handle multiple tasks and work
 - independently

- Knowledge of HR Software
- Innovative
- Service Focused

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu

Punjabi

INTERESTS

- Spending time with Friends & Family
- Use of Social Media

Playing Cricket

